businessfinancenews.com 2016-05-15

# Privacy Policy

BusinessFinanceNews places a high value on the privacy of its users. This Privacy Policy (“PP”) sets out

the types of information that we may collect from users of www.businessfinancenews.com (the

“Website”) and the purposes for which we may use such information. The PP and the Terms of Use

(“TOU”) constitute a legally binding agreement between you and BusinessFinanceNews If you do not

agree to any part of the PP and/or TOU, you must not use the website. The PP may be modified from

time to time and you are advised to check this page regularly.

INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED

In addition to the other types of UGC that BusinessFinanceNews may collect from you and that may be

used by it according to the licenses set forth in the TOU, BusinessFinanceNews may collect personally-

identifiable information (called “personal information” in this PP) submitted to BusinessFinanceNews,

including (but not limited to) information submitted when registering an account with us or filling out

other forms.

This “personal information” may include (but not be limited to) your:

Name

Gender

Date of birth

Occupation

Income range

Home and/or work address

Email address

Telephone Numbers

BusinessFinanceNews may also periodically collect log files, including IP addresses, from our server.

These files give a general picture of who is visiting the Website and which pages are being viewed most

often. This information is collected to assist us in the maintenance and administration of the Website.

Log files are collected mainly for research purposes to see what pages are of most interest and use to

current and potential clients as well as to gather demographic, geographic and economic trends.

BusinessFinanceNews reserves the right to make changes to this policy's description of log files use at

any time.

USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

You hereby agree that BusinessFinanceNews may use your personal information for the following

purposes:

Administering the Website

Personalizing the Website for you

Sending you marketing communications, including on behalf of third party advertisers, provided such

advertisers will not be provided access to your personally-identifiable information

Sending you other electronic communications

Enabling your access and use of the Website

Monitoring compliance with the TOU

Allowing you to use interactive features of the Website

SECURITY

BusinessFinanceNews will exercise reasonable care, including taking technical and organisational

precautions, in order to protect your personal data from unauthorized access or use. Your personal

information will only be stored on secure servers owned, controlled or contracted for by

BusinessFinanceNews. If BusinessFinanceNews contracts out its data hosting to a third party, we will

endeavor to ensure that party has agreed to comply with our privacy standards as described in this PP.

Despite BusinessFinanceNews’s obligations to make reasonable efforts to protect personal information

as set forth above, BusinessFinanceNews cannot provide perfect security, and will not be responsible or

liable for damage, pecuniary or otherwise, caused by a third party’s unauthorized access to or use of

your personal information. Further, BusinessFinanceNews shall not be responsible for maintaining or

storing your personal information or other UGC for any particular period of time.

DATA TRANSFER

Your personal information may be transferred internationally between the countries in which

BusinessFinanceNews maintains a presence in order to enable the use of your data as specified in the

PP.

CHILD PRIVACY

BusinessFinanceNews considers the privacy of children to be especially important and prohibits children

under the age of 16 from sending their personal information over the internet without their

parent/guardian’s permission.

THIRD PARTY SITES

The Website may contain links to third party sites. BusinessFinanceNews is not responsible for the

practices of third parties and encourages users to read their privacy policies before using their websites.

DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES

We do not share any of the personal information you provide to us with any third party other than

service providers of ours who assist us in providing the information and/or services we are providing to

you. To the extent that we do share your personal information with a service provider, we will endeavor

to ensure that party has agreed to comply with our privacy standards as described in this PP.

OTHER PERSONS’ PERSONAL INFORMATION

In using the Website, you may acquire access to others’ personal information, such as names and

addresses. Your use of the Website constitutes your agreement to respect others’ privacy with respect

to personal information. You may not, under any circumstances, release others’ personal information to

third parties, including your employees who have no need for the information, without the written

consent of both BusinessFinanceNews and the person or persons whose personal information you

intend to forward. You may not, under any circumstances, use personal information obtained from the

Website to send unsolicited email, facsimile transmissions, or spam, even if the person to whom you

intend to send unsolicited email or spam has communicated with you in the past. You agree to

immediately notify BusinessFinanceNews of any release or breach of any third party’s personal

information (including name, address, phone numbers, email addresses, account numbers, investment

histories, or social security number) that occurs as a result of use of the Website under your user name.
